export default  [
	{
		"question": "99 x 75 =",
		"option1" : "1226",
		"option2": "6541",
		"option3": "7425",
		"option4": "8450",
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "3 x 3,4 =",
		"option1" : "10,1",
		"option2": "11",
		"option3": "10,2",
		"option4": "9,5",
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "15,15 : 3 =",
		"option1" : "5,05",
		"option2": "5,45",
		"option3": "6,05",
		"option4": "4.55",
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "8 +12 : 4 x 2 =",
		"option1": "10,15",
		"option2": "9,35",
		"option3": "11,51",
		"option4": "10,86",
		"answer": 4
	},
	{
		"question": "14 x 260 =",
		"option1": "3640",
		"option2": "4500",
		"option3": "3205",
		"option4": "3005",
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "35% van 200",
		"option1": "95",
		"option2": "75",
		"option3": "70",
		"option4": "85",
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "65% van 700",
		"option1": "584",
		"option2": "542",
		"option3": "455",
		"option4": "600",
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "1344 + 898 =",
		"option1": "2954",
		"option2": "2541",
		"option3": "3254",
		"option4": "2242",
		"answer": 4
	},
	{
		"question": "74 : 0.2 = ",
		"option1": "421",
		"option2": "385",
		"option3": "350",
		"option4": "370",
		"answer": 4
	},
	{
		"question": "75% van 7,60",
		"option1": "6,7",
		"option2": "5,7",
		"option3": "5,2",
		"option4": "7,1",
		"answer": 2
	}
]